I have been programming since 8th grade and have worked on a variety of different projects. I've reverse engineered kernel byte code, created deep learning models, implemented network protocols, and done full stack web development. I want to work on technology that will change the world and make people's lives easier.

585-465-3716 axs9701@rit.edu

Graduate GPA: 4.0 Undergrad GPA: 3.61

Languages

- C#
- PHP
- C++
- Python
- Javascript
- Scala
- SQL
- HTML
- CSS

Software

- Linux
- Git
- React
- Docker
- Postgres
- MongoDB
- Jenkins

Notable Classes Taken

- Deep Learning
- Web Security
- Computer Networks
- Intro to Big Data
- Parallel Systems
- Embedded Systems
- Computer Graphics
- Algorithms
- OOP Design
- Stellar Astrophysics

Education

RIT — Masters in Computer Science, Bachelors in Software Engineering,
Minor in Computer Security
Graduating December 2020

Work Experience

Tesla, Software Engineer Intern — Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

I worked directly with product managers to create internal front-end applications using React, Typescript, and GraphQL. I've also contributed to simulation software written in Python.

Datto, Software Engineer Intern — May 2019 - Aug 2019

I worked on a distributed system for backing up petabytes of data consisting of a Scala, PHP, and Ruby backend with an AngularJS frontend. I developed features for a processing pipeline and fixed critical issues affecting customer backups.

EagleView, Software Engineer Co-Op — Jan 2018 - Aug 2018

I worked with a scrum team doing full stack web development for both customer facing applications and internal micro-services. I worked with Postgres databases, a PHP backend, a JS frontend, and HTML/CSS. I also started a micro-service in Go for my team along with Jenkins jobs to test it and deploy it to Kubernetes.

RSA, Software Engineer Co-Op — Jan 2017 - Aug 2017

I developed an algorithm to remove hole punch marks from scanned documents using a deep learning model that I trained. I also implemented printer network protocols in C# after using Wireshark for analysis and integrated this into existing software..

Personal Projects

Garbage Full Detector - https://github.com/Experiment5X/GarbageFullDetector

A deep learning classifier that runs on a Raspberry Pi with a camera to detect if my garbage is full and notify people when it hasn't been taken out.

Feature Map Viewer - https://github.com/Experiment5X/DeepFeatureVisualizationWebApp An application for generating visualizations of feature maps in the CNN VGG-16.

GscInterpreter - https://github.com/Experiment5X/GscInterpreter

An interpreter for the scripting language used in Call of Duty written entirely in Haskell.

Velocity - https://github.com/hetelek/Velocity

A cross-platform desktop application for managing proprietary Xbox360 files and bypassing security measures with over 150,000 downloads.